greenwinnetwork.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy Policy « Greenwin Network

## Privacy Policy Statement

This is the web site of Green Win network Ltd.  
Registered office address:  
Lawford House, Albert Place, London, N3 1RL, United Kingdom

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

We collect no information on consumers who browse our Web pages.

With respect to cookies: A cookie is placed on your computer when visiting the Sqip website. This cookie, which has duration of 60 days, is used to track referral signups.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please contact us.

With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of information such as financial information, we redirect members to a secure server. We have appropriate security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that the member has provided.

Green Win Network does not reveal your phone number to other users. The only time we collect your phone number from you is when you enter your phone number on our website.

The phone number at which you receive calls will be verified to ensure that the person providing the phone number is in possession of said phone. Verification of your phone enables other people to call your phone.

We may also collect your email address to send updates, voicemail notification, a newsletter or news regarding the service. We collect your email from you when you enter your email into our website. Verification of your email allows you to receive voicemail messages from other users attempting to contact you.

As part of the registration process, you may be asked to create a username and password to be associated with your persona for security. We may also collect your name, country, or other relevant data to enhance security/facilitate Services.

By using our website, we are able to and may track certain non-personally-identifiable information about you and your correspondence with the Green Win Network web site in order to perform internal research on our users’ demographics, interests and behaviour. This information may include the URL from which you arrived, your click path within the Green Win Network site, the next URL you may visit, what browser you are using and your IP address.

Green Win Network Ltd uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring compliance with our terms and policies, to improve the user experience with our services, and to customize Web page and widget content based on browser type and user profile information. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set — each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

Please note that Green Win Network Ltd may allow third party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer.

Advertisers’ use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the Green Win Network Ltd Privacy Policy.

Your Personal Information will not be shared with third parties except to provide the services you’ve requested. In order to provide the services you’ve requested, we carefully choose partners to work with.

These partners are technology providers of telecoms and other approved services, which are an ingredient in the Green Win Network services. These partners are required to protect your information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy and do not have any independent right to share your Green Win Network member Information.

We may use non-identifying information to better design our services. Green Win Network Ltd works with third party advertiser/cookies who may use information about your visit to the website to provide them with ads.

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, we will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Green Win Network Ltd, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Green Win Network Ltd Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service.

Green Win Network Ltd reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Green Win Network Ltd or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest.

Certain information or services offered or provided through this website, from time to time, may be provided on or through other websites operated by or in conjunction with third party providers (“Partners”). Although Green Win Network Ltd will continue to control any personally identifiable information collected about you from one of these sites, such information may be shared by Green Win Network Ltd with that Partner in order to further facilitate the Services to which you register. However, a Partner will not rent, sell, or disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless you consent to such disclosures and use in advance (for example, you may be asked to opt-in on a particular co-branded site in order to receive information or offers from a Partner, its affiliates or agents).

We are committed to keeping your Green Win Network member information private, and will use that information only for purposes of operating our services and improving them.

We have implemented security guidelines to help safeguard the privacy of your information from unauthorized access or improper use.

We have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect and we will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available.

You may use Green Win Network telecoms and other communications services to receive phone calls which are partly or fully handled via our telecommunications partners. Therefore any information which you may communicate during such phone calls, including any personal information, shall not be deemed private. We cannot guarantee the security of such information, that you disclose or communicate in such phone calls and you do so at your own risk.

If you believe that the Green Win Network web site is not following its stated information policy, please contact us immediately.
